Craig Seymour Collection, 1968-2006 SC 144
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 5. Audiovisual (excluding interviews)
  - 5.2. Commercial media, Nearly 1,000 CDs of commercially released audio is included in this collection. The CDs are a mixture of published and unpublished releases. The unpublished releases are primarily promotional copies sent out in advance of an album release for review. The unpublished record
    - Dirty South Remix [Single] // Goodie Mob., 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3462
      LFPCD-4203
    - You've got a Friend [Single] // The Brand New Heavies, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3463
      FFRR
      570 013-2
    - Lately I [Single] // Evans, Faith, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3464
      Bad Boy
      BBPCD-9257
    - Rafiki Mixes [Single] // Zap Mama, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3465
      Luaka Bop
      70876-15222-2-8
    - Think of You; Let's Get Down [Single] // Tony Toni Toné, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3466
      Mercury
      314 574 489-2
    - Just a lil' Bit [Single] // Dejah, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3467
      Un-D-Nyaable
      UND 0003 20
    - Heartbreaker [Single] // Carey, Mariah, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3468
      CSK 42813
    - Lost My Mind [Single] // Hawkins, Jamie, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3469
      PRCD 7459-2
    - We Will Find a Way [Single] // Adams, Oleta; Russell, Brenda, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3470
      RDJ 62909-2
    - Krazy [Single] // Dejah, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3471
      UND 0005
    - Boom Biddy Bye Bye [Single] // Cypruss Hill, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3472
      CSK 8075
    - Borrowed Time [Single] // Porter, Billy, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3473
      DV8 Records
      DVSAD 00566
    - Ghetto Love [Single] // Da Brat (Musician), 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3474
      Promo; Duplicate of 1513?
      44K 78508
    - Ask of You [Single] // Saadiq, Raphael, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3475
      BSK 7082
    - The Cupher: Part 3 [Single] // Cutlass, Frankie, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3476
      Relativity
      RPROCD 0498
    - I will Go With You (Con Te Partiró) [Single] // Summer, Donna, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3477
      49K 79202
    - Deliver Me [Single] // 3Dee; Procter, Michael, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3478
      Bassline
      BLR-013
    - Crewz Pop [Single] // DA Youngsta's, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3479
      PRCD 4979-2
    - Makes me Wanna Die; Here Comes the Aliens [Single] // Tricky, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3480
      BRCD 348-854 934-2
    - We Are family [Single], 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3481
      TBCD 2331
    - Dolly My Baby [Single] // Super Cat (Musician), 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3482
      CSK 4957
    - Found Love [Single] // Cardwell, Joi, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3483
      Eightball records
      EBCD123
    - All My Love [Single] // Queen Pen, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3484
      INTDS-97023
    - It's all about you not Me [Single] // Spencer, Tracie, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3485
      DPRO 7087 6 13530 2 0
    - Just Another Day [Single] // Latifah, Queen, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3486
      3746348502
    - So Gone [Single} // Monica, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3487
      J1DJ-21260-2
    - Thoia Thoing [Single] // Kelly, R., 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3488
      JDJ-40105-2
    - Pull up to the Bumper [single] // Patra, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3489
      BSK 7094
    - Yours Faithfully [Single] // Jackson, Rebbie, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3490
      MJJ
      OSK 3261
    - Fly Girl; Nature of a Sista' [Single] // Latifah, Queen, 1991; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3491
      TBCD 991
    - No Pigeons [Single] // Sporty Thievz, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3492
      Ruffhouse
      38K 79190
    - Back & Forth [Single] // Aaliyah, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3493
      Blackground Enterprises
      jdj-42173-2
    - Journey to the Past [Single] // Aaliyah, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3494
      Atlantic PRCD 8380-2
    - All Day, All Night [Single] // Mills, Stephanie, 1957-, 1992; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3495
      MCA5P-2487
    - Always and Forever Live from Royal Albert Hall [Single] // Vandross, Luther, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3496
      ESK 6664
    - Throw You Down [Single] // Houston, Thelma, 1991; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3497
      9 40080-2
    - Make up your Mind [Single] // Lynn, Veronica, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3498
      RDJ 62876-2
    - Caught out There [Single] // Kelis, 1980-, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3499
      7087 6 14382 2 2
    - When Will I See you Smile Again [Single] // Bell, Ricky, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3500
      CSK 41497
    - Knoc [Single] // Knoc-Turn'Al, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3501
      PRCD 1724
    - Doesn't Really Matter [Single] // Jackson, Janet, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3502
      Defr 15100-2
    - Time After Time [Single] // Inoj, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3503
      CSK 41348
    - Hey Papi [Single] // Jay-Z, 1969-, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3504
      DEFR 15106-2
    - Ripgroove [Single] // Double 99, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3505
      Logic
      74321-51764-2
    - You Make Me Feel Brand New [Single] // Belle, Regina, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3506
      CSK 7516
    - Hold On [Single] // Nesby, Ann, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3507
      Perspective
      21458 13152
    - None of Your Business; Shoop [Single] // Salt-n-Pepa (Musical group), 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3508
      London
      857 715-2
    - Uh Huh [Single] // Terri & Monica, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3509
      ESK 5375
    - Love Child [Single] // Sweet Sensation, 1990; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3510
      7 96487-2
    - Take Your Time; Thug Devotion [Single] // Tré, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3511
      Mo Things
      88561-1586-2
    - Excerpts from the colored Section [EP] // Donnie, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3512
      Giant Step
      GSTP7019-2
    - Night in Harlem [Single] // Vandross, Luther, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3513
      7087 6 13169 2 6 DPRO-13169
    - Miss My Lovin' [Single] // 4Kast, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3514
      RDJ 65401-2
    - Touch It [Single] // Monifah, 1972-, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3515
      UPTDS-56207
    - Old School Lovin' [Single] // Moore, Chanté, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3516
      LSJ5P-3150
    - The Right Time [Single] // Cherrelle, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3517
      PW-200
    - Missing You; The Difference Between Us [Single] // Turner, Tina, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3518
      7243 8 83085 2 6
    - Slow Down [Single] // Covington, Trisha, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3519
      CSK 7208
    - If You want It [Single] // Soul For Real, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3520
      UPT5P-3480
    - Why Does it Hurt so Bad; I Wanna Dance With Somebody [Single] // Houston, Whitney, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3521
      07822-13214-2
    - I Know [Single] // Vandross, Luther, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3522
      7087 6 13639 2 0 DPRO-13639
    - Crazy [Single] // Daisy Dee, 1991; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3523
      LMR
      2790-2-RDJ
    - Love Thing [Single] // Turner, Tina, 1991; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3524
      DPRO-79947
    - Can't Hang [Single] // Xscape (Musical group), 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3525
      CSK 7858
    - Jam [Single] // Jackson, Michael, 1958-, 1991; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3526
      49K 74334
    - Bow Wow [That's My Name] [Single] // Bow Wow (Musician), 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3527
      So So Def
      44K 79487
    - Again [Single] // Kravitz, Lenny, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3528
      7087 6 16147 2 5 DPRO-16147
    - Where Love Lives [Single] // Limerick, Alison, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3529
      74321-98844-2
    - Hold Me [Single] // Steele, Jevetta, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3530
      CSK 77106
    - Learn 2 Luv [Single] // English, Kim, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3531
      Nervous
      20248
    - The Underground; Reach Up [Single] // Celeda, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3532
      Star Sixty Nine
      STAR CD 509
    - Champagne [Single] // Salt-n-Pepa (Musical group), 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3533
      MCA5P-3808
    - I Want You Back [Single] // Melanie B, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3534
      8087 6 13605 2 3 DPRO 13605
    - Romeo Must Die [Single] // Timbaland; Magoo, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3535
      7087 6 15709 2 2 DPRO-15709
    - Neck UV DA Woods [Single] // Mystikal; Outkast, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3536
      Lil' man/Interscope
      JDJ-42608
    - That Man of Mine [Single] // Sugarshop, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3537
      Red Zone
      RZI1998-CD1
    - Hit On Me [Single] // Johnson, Syleena, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3538
      JDJ-42981-2
    - Jazzy Belle [Single] // Outkast, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3539
      LFPCD-4236
    - Survivor [Single] // Destiny's Child (Musical group), 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3540
      CSK 16462
    - Crazy [Single] // Michele, Yvette, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3541
      RDJ 64901-2
    - Sweet Dreams [Single] // Nas, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3542
      CSK 9203
    - Stand Right Up [Single] // Stingily, Byron, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3543
      20415
    - Affection [Single] // Watley, Jody, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3544
      Avitone
      BLR 74506-2
    - Get Rich to This [Single] // Goodie Mob., 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3545
      LFPCD-4442
    - My Side of the Story [Single] // Gilbert, Nicci, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3549
      MCAR 25712-2
    - Southern Gul [Single] // Badu, Erykah, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3550
      U5P-1587
    - Infatuation [Single] // Laurneá, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3551
      Yab Yum
      ESK 2473
    - Little Miracles (Happen Every Day) [EP] // Vandross, Luther, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3552
      Epic/Liv
      34K 74945
    - Wait (The Wisper song) [Single] // Ying Yang Twins, 2005; 1 Audio Disc
      TVT
      TV-2525-2P
    - Miss You [Single] // Aaliyah, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3553
      UNIR 20900-2
    - Nothin' Move but the Money [Single] // Mic. Geronimo, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3554
      Blunt
      TVT 4939-2
    - Above the Rim [Sigle] // Bell Biv DeVoe (Musical group), 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3555
      MCA5P-2631
    - Voice of Freedom [Single] // Williams, Freedom, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3556
      44K 74943
    - Let the Beat Hit 'Em [Single] // Lisa Lisa, 1991; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3557
      CSK 73847
    - Pass the Courvoisier [Single] // Busta Rhymes (Musician), 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3558
      J1DJ 21155 2
    - Trans DF Express [Single] // Dungeon Family, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3559
      ARPCD-5046
    - Stella's Favorite Grooves: How Stella got her Groove Back [EP], 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3560
      Flyte Tyme
      MCAD-11806
    - The Life [EP] // Keys, Alicia, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3561
      J1DJ-21008-2
    - Independent Women [Single] // Destiny's Child (Musical group), 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3562
      44K 79493
    - I Like It [EP] // Sammie, 1987-, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3563
      C2 7243 8 58776 2 9
    - The Boy is Mine [Single] // Brandy & Monica, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3564
      ATLANTIC 2-84118
    - Last Night's Letter/ I Care 'Bout You [Single] // K-Ci & JoJo, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3565
      MCADM-55391
    - La-La-La- (Excuse Me Again) [Single] // Jay-Z, 1969-, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3566
      UNIR21009-2
    - Take You Out/ Can Heaven Wait/ Bring Your Heart to Mine [Single] // Vandross, Luther, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3567
    - They don't Understand Me [EP] // Esperanza, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3568
      LFPCD-4381
    - Bounce With Me [Single] // Lil Bow Wow (Musician), 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3569
      44K 79476
    - Come See Me [Single] // 112 (Musical group), 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3570
      78612-79076-2
    - Keep Lovin' You [Single] // Hollister, Dave, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3571
      MCAR 25742-2
    - Treat You Like a Queen [Single] // Patterson, Rahsaan, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3572
      MCA5P-4383
    - What Did I do to You? [Single] // Ellis, Terry, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3573
      Prcd 9448-2
    - Da Baddest Bitch [Single] // Trina, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3574
      PRCD 300010
    - My Up and Down [Single] // Howard, Adina, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3575
      PRCD 9235-2
    - The Boomin' System [Single] // LL Cool J, 1968-, 1990; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3576
      CSK 73457
    - Colors of Love [Single] // Fischer, Lisa, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3577
      PRCD 8773-2
    - Missing You [Single] // Brandy; Tamia; Knght, Gladys; Khan, Chaka, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3578
      Prcd-9610-2
    - Nobody Else [Single] // Peniston, CeCe, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3579
      Silk
      SENT 9802-2
    - Wide Open [Single] // LeShaun, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3580
      TBCD 582
    - Geto Heaven [Single] // Common (Musician); Gray, Macy, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3581
      MCA 25279-2
    - Hey Lover [Single] // LL Cool J, 1968-, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3582
      314 577 495-2
    - Straight Up [Single] // Moore, Chanté, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3583
      MCAR-25215-2
    - U-R-A-Ho (And You Don't Know) [Single] // Wright, Betty, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3584
      Ms. B
      MSBCD-9912
    - Let's Stay Together [Single] // Benét, Eric, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3585
      9 17656-2
    - Give Me You [Single] // Blige, Mary J., 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3586
      MCAR 25031-2
    - Slam [Single] // Onyx (Musical group), 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3587
      JmJ
      OSK 4965
    - Saturday Nite [Single] // The Brand New Heavies, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3588
      3984 29575 2 BNCDP12
    - Dream on Dreamer [Single] // The Brand New Heavies, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3589
      Delicious Vinyl
      2-95952
    - All Good? [Single] // De La Soul (Musical group), 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3590
      TBCD 2178
    - Look 4 Tha Name [Single] // Blade, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3591
      7087 6 15755 2 1 DPR-15755
    - Sugar Buddy [Single] // Nodesha, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3592
      82876-54282-2
    - Luxury Cococure [Single] // Maxwell, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3593
      CSK 4222
    - Star: Album Snippets [EP] // 702 (Musical group), 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3594
      440 019 583-2
    - Milk is my Sugar [Ep] // Skunk Anansie (Musical group), 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3595
      One Little Indian/Epic
      ESK 9995
    - Feelin' Freaky [Single] // Cannon, Nick, 1980-, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3596
      Nick
      JDJ-49516-2
    - Can't Nobody Hold me Down [Single] // Diddy, 1969-, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3597
      BBPCD-9082
    - What About Us [Single] // Jodeci (Musical group), 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3598
      UPT5P-3035
    - Reality [Single] // Evans, Adriana, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3599
      RDJ 64712-2
    - Come Over [Single] // Evans, Faith, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3600
      BBPCD-9065
    - Watch What You Say [Single] // Guru (Musical group), 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3601
      F2-58438
    - Lapdance [Single] // N.E.R.D. (Musical group), 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3602
      7087 6 12252 2 B DPRO-12252
    - Work It [Single] // Elliott, Missy, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3603
      Goldmine
      PRCD 1830-2
    - Intentions [Single] // Terri & Monica, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3604
      ESK 5688
    - Every Nation [Single] // Red Hot R&B All Stars, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3605
      CSK 3791
    - Sampler [EP] // The Product G&B, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3606
      J1JDJ-21033-2
    - When you get Right Down to it [Single] // Hyman, Phyllis, 1991; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3614
      Philadelphia International
      ZP17047-2
    - Can't trust Nobody [Single] // Sloppy (Musical group), 1992; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3615
      Active/Select
      PRCD 8679
    - Love Comes and Goes [EP] // ED O.G; DA Bulldogs (Musical group), 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3616
      CDP 1153
    - First Choice [Single] // Doctor Love, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3617
      Double J
      2573-2
    - Sound of Da Police [Single] // KRS-One (Musician), 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3618
      JDJ-42191-2
    - Voices of the Heart/ If You're not Gonna Love me Right [Single] // Ross, Diana, 1944-, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3619
      374631392-2
    - Do You [Single] // Heather B., 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3620
      MCA5P-4195
    - I Wanna Be Down [Single] // Brandy, 1979-, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3621
      PRCD 5936
    - How's it Goin' Down [Single] // D M X, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3622
      DEF 257-2
    - I've Had enough [Single] // Mizelle, Cindy, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3623
      PRCD 5727
    - Party Ain't a Party [Single] // Queen Pen, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3624
      INT5P-6315
    - If You Believe [Single] // Savage, Chantay, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3625
      I.D./BMG
      RDJ 62494-2
    - Don't Let it go to Your Head [Single] // Savage, Chantay, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3626
      RDJ 62571-2
    - Triflin' [Single] // Coko, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3627
      RDJ-65969-2
    - Do Right [Single] // King, Evelyn "Champange", 1990; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3628
      DPRO 4589
    - As If We Never Met [Single] // Moore, Chanté, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3629
      LSJ5P-2689
    - Clock Strikes [Single] // Timbaland; Magoo, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3630
      Blackground/Atlantic
      PRCD 8435
    - One Woman Man [Single] // Hollister, Dave, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3631
      Def Squad/Dreamworks
      DRMR-13694-2
    - Pull Over [Single] // Trina, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3632
      Slip n Slide/ Atlantic
      PRCD 300367
    - What About This Love [Single] // Mr. Fingers, 1992; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3633
      MCA3P-2393
    - Laid Back Girl [Single] // Maze (Musical group), 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3634
      PRO-CD-6566-R
    - Where My Girls At? [Single] // 702 (Musical group), 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3635
      U5P-1481
    - Good 4 We [Single] // D-Influence, 1992; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3636
      PRCD 4831-2
    - We Gotta Run [Single] // Casserine, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3637
      PRO-CD-7294
    - Is That Your Chick [Single] // Memphis Bleek, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3638
      DEFR 15111-2
    - Wait a Minute [Single] // Ray J, 1981-, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3641
      PRCD 300452
    - Knockin' [Single] // Grant, Angel, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3642
      U5P-1383
    - Stranger in my House [Single] // Tamia, 1976-, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3643
      PRCD 1579-2
    - Sock it 2 Me [Single] // Elliott, Missy, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3644
      PRCD 9894-2
    - Drop/Rollout [Single] // Timbaland; Magoo, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3645
    - Come Home to Me [Single] // Howard, Miki, 1989; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3646
      PRCD 3455-2
    - Movin' on [Single] // Mya, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3647
      INT5P-6458
    - It's Hard Sometimes [Single] // Knuckles, Frankie, 1991; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3648
      PRCD 4037
    - I Don't Want to Fight [Single] // Turner, Tina, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3649
      DPRO 12807
    - Swing my Way [Single] // K.P.; ENVYI, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3650
      PRCD 7319-2
    - Livin' For Love [Single] // Cole, Natalie, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3651
      Prcd 1554-2
    - We Getz Down [Single] // Rampage, 1975-, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3653
      Prcd 9911-2
    - Fabulous [Single] // Jaheim (Musician), 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3654
      PRO-CDR-100980
    - Everybody on the Line Outside [Single] // Flipmode Squad, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3655
      PRCD 1146-2
    - Think About You [Single] // Blackstreet (Musical group), 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3656
      INT5P-6587
    - Make it Hot [Single] // Nicole, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3657
      PRCD 1108 2
    - Work that Body [Single] // Chanelle, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3658
      Great Jones
      PRCD 629-2
    - The Rain (Supa Dupa Fly) [Single] // Elliott, Missy, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3659
      PRCD 9833-2
    - Morning [Single] // McWilliams, Brigette, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3660
      7087 6 12743 2 5 DPRO 12743
    - Bling Bling [Single] // B.G., 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3661
      U5P-1555
    - The Soul of Lenny [EP] // Kravitz, Lenny, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3662
      7087 6 13144 2 7 DPRO-13144
    - Who Am I [EP] // Blade, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3663
    - Boogie Down [EP] // Funky Derrick., 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3664
      TW3P-90152
    - Fast Lane [Single] // Bilal, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3665
      INTR-10522-2
    - It's Been You [Single] // Baker, Anita, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3666
      PRCD 9224-2
    - Get the Hell On (Get Gone) [Single] // Ideal, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3667
      7087 6 14321 2 1 DPRO-14321
    - B R Right [Single] // Trina, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3668
      Slip-n-Slide/ Atlantic
      PRCD 301096
    - Hit 'Em Wit Da Hee [Single] // Elliott, Missy, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3669
      PRCD 7318-2
    - You / I Like/I Like it [Single] // Powell, Jesse, 1971-, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3670
      Silas/MCA
      LSJ5P-3907
    - U Got That Love (Call it a Night) [Single] // Levert, Gerald, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3671
      Prcd 1922
    - Understanding [Single] // Xscape (Musical group), 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3672
      So So Def/Columbia
      CSK 5667
    - This is the Right Time [Single] // Stansfield, Lisa, 1990; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3673
      ASCD-2069
    - Shine [EP] // Crawford, Randy, 1992; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3674
      PRO-CD-5351
    - Tonight's the Night [Single] // Blackstreet (Musical group), 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3675
      PRCD 6311
    - Take Away [Single] // Elliott, Missy, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3676
      Goldmine/EEG
      PRCD 1708-2
    - Formal Invite [Single] // Ray J, 1981-, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3677
      PRCD 300645
    - DJ Will You Please Play [Single] // Raheem, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3678
      Tight 2 Def
      Tight 2 Def 4499-2
    - Keep on Jumpin' [Single] // Terry, Todd, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3681
      FESCD 11/ 578257-2
    - Sunshine [Single] // Gabrielle, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3682
      Go Beat
      GOBCD23 561 366-2
    - Give Me the Night [Single] // Crawford, Randy, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3683
      WEA
      WEA142CD 3984 21016 2
    - One Day [Single] // D-MOB (Musical group), 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3684
      BA 940 FCD239 FFRR 851 669-2
    - Like Dreamers Do [Single] // Paris, Mica, 1988; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3685
      BRCDP 108
    - I'm Going all the way [Single] // Sounds of Blackness (Musical group), 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3686
      587 483-2
    - Everything is Gonna be Alright [Single] // Sounds of Blackness (Musical group), 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3687
      587 467-2
    - Up and Down [Single] // Cox, Deborah, 1974-, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3688
    - Get Up On It [Single] // Sweat, Keith, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3689
      EKR196CD 7559-66167-2
    - Get It Up (The Feeling) [Single] // Ultra Naté (Musician), 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3690
      Orange
      ORCDM53712
    - Everybody's a Star [Single] // Simpson, Paul, 1989; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3691
      662 584
    - Close to You [Single] // The Brand New Heavies, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3692
      BNHCD7
    - Unltimate Trunk Funk [Ep] // The Brand New Heavies, 1992; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3693
      FCD 185
    - Ready for a New Day [Single] // Terry, Todd, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3694
      FESCD 40/568 701-2
    - I'LL Be Around [Single] // Crawford, Randy, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3695
      8573 82112-2
    - Voices in my Mind [Single] // Sound of Ministry, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3696
      Ministry of Sound
      SOMCD 003